The past year, we have been on a remarkable journey,
moving fearlessly forward.
The University of Maryland continues to excel
thanks to the hard work and dedication
of our students, faculty, staff, alumni, and friends.
Together, we are taken on the world's grand challenges,
united in purpose to improve the lives of all human kind
and to do good.
As we look ahead to the coming year,
let's celebrate our collective accomplishments
and recommit ourselves to creating a better future.
During this holiday season,
I hope you find time to rest, reflect,
and cherish the moments with your loved ones.
From our home to yours,
may the holidays bring you,
your families and communities, joy and peace.